Piotr Tajanowicz

PHP Software Developer

PHONE (48) 663 559 826

NATIONALITY polish

EMAIL piotr.tajanowicz@gmail.com

LINKS <u>Linkedin</u>, <u>GitHub</u>

Profile

Dedicated and experienced Software Developer with extensive knowledge of engineering principles, theories, specifications, and standards. Substantial knowledge and experience with web applications development and bash scripts. Over nine years of experience on work for both the UK and European Markets.

Employment History

Mar 2017 - Present

WROCLAW

Software Developer

IBM Global Services Delivery Centre Poland

Write, modify, integrate software code

Maintain existing computer programs by making modifications as required

Identify and communicate technical problems, processes and solutions

Assist in the development of logical and physical specifications

Mar 2012 - Mar 2017

WROCŁAW

Web Developer

Motor-Presse Poland

Write, modify, integrate software code

Develop Web sites architecture and determine hardware and software requirements

Plan, design, write, modify, integrate Web-sites related code

Create and optimize content for the Web sites using a variety of graphics, database, animation and other software

Jun 2011 - May 2012

WROCŁAW

Web Developer

Allegro Group Poland

Write, modify, integrate software code

Create and optimize content for the Web sites using a variety of graphics, database, animation and other software

Develop Web sites architecture and determine hardware and software requirements

Assist in the development of logical and physical specifications

May 2010 - Apr 2011

WROCŁAW

Web Programmer

Comes Poland

Write, modify, integrate software code

Plan, design, write, modify, integrate Web-site related code

Develop Web sites architecture and determine hardware and software requirements

Education

Oct 2003 - Nov 2008

WROCŁAW

Wroclaw University of Economics

Master's Degree

Field: Computer Science and Econometrics

Specialization: E-Business

-	 118

PHP
Laravel Framework

ZEND framework

CakePHP

SOLID Principles

Design Patterns (MVC, Factory, etc)

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Vue Framework

jQuery

Bootstrap

DB2

SQL Linux Docker

Node.js Git

Java Pyhon

D3.js graphs framework



Traveling the World, doing sport activities like riding a bike or swimming, and what is the most important, spending time with my family

Languages

English

••••

German



Courses

Oct 2019

IELTS exam taken with band 6.5 achieved

British Council

Sep 2018

Mastering PHP Design Patterns

IBM Services

IBM Genera	l Data	Protection	Regulation	(GDPR
IDIVI OCITCIO	ı Data	1 10tection	Negulation	ו ושטו

IBM Services

Aug 2017 Agile@IBM - A Taste of Agile

IBM Services

Mar 2017 Building Dynamic Web Sites with MySQL and PHP

SkillSoft

Mar 2017 Developing PHP Applications for IBM Data Servers

IBM Services